alright everyone here's the deal we we
go down to Gaza send a hawk and tell
them that it's a joke gun in not bamas
killer that's a clear famines name yeah
and my just doing it next time sounds
like a plan let's go everyone wait huh
everyone look up up here in the sky huh
what's what's up the shoe rack it's a
bird no it's a plane no it's Superman
Sonic I have come to tell you the truth
Batman is lying to you huh what do you
mean Superman how's baman lying to me he
just told me that he's not killing
people saw he is Batman turned evil oh
no no you can't be telling the truth
he's my new friend no sock he is not you
oh no sock look huh no let go see PPO
now get outta here right now Oh help me
so late no no oh God that's what
happened I'm a nice oh no you killed
c-3po soup man you have to do something
I do Batman you have killed far too many
people I cannot let you live
ah I'd like to you catch me [ __ ]
goodbye oh no he got away what we gonna
do Superman don't worry he's just he
can't fly like me nobody's at super
speed there's no way you can get away
from me yeah I guess you're right
Superman huh what oh no what is it Sonic
behind you famines got a sword yes not
my man oh it's a song made of kryptonite
ah Sonic run haha I'm coming from ya
Batman Oh Oh No help me somebody help me
you let go of Sonic right now na na
hurtin me um you bend over like a little
[ __ ] you are oh now no Superman you
can't kill him remember what you always
say you do not kill people what changed
my mind on Sonic hurt man Superman
please I'm begging you have to let him
go you shut up you're next fat ass oh no
oh no no Sonic where you go and earn me
ushalla I'm gosh of this sort right up
your
nah yeah had me take a gun price
you